Nicholas Dziewit 1620 S. Mole St. Philadelphia, PA 19145 215-422-2179

nicholas.dziewit@gmail.com

Objective

It is my intention to utilize my years of retail and marketing experience in conjunction with my web development skills to utilize a position overseeing and producing innovative and interesting applications for consumers and brands alike.

Education

UPenn LPS Full Stack Web Development Coding Boot Camp, 2020-Current Philadelphia University, Digital Design, 2007-2009

Experience

Urban Outfitters, August 2009 - June 2014

- Utilization of company sales reports to create weekly and monthly merchandising plans and layout for maximization of sales focusing on top 10 items of each class/department
- Working with teams at both home office and flagship stores to analyze and predict current trends to create different concepts for upcoming seasons for both national and local markets

UNIQLO, June 2014 - May 2017

- Collaborated with a international brand to open a flagship store in Philadelphia, utilizing demographics and local knowledge to create a unique stocklist for the Philadelphia market and help to establish a local identity within the company
- Established a new company standard in terms of display & presentation that lead to visits from the CEO to collaborate on new company guidelines for processing merchandise while still maintaining a high level of customer service and staying under budget

Freelance Event Producer, November 2012 - Current

- Analyzing local markets and music trends to produce high-attending, interesting, and unique events in the Philadelphia area with satellite parties across the country
- Established an identity in the city as a quality and reliable promoter and DJ that's capable to accommodate to various sized venues and demographics
- Curates and manages multiple social media accounts to engage with local markets for both organic and paid growth and reach

Skills

Front end web design and development (HTML5, CSS, Javascript, ¡Query, Bootstrap,) Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Premiere, Illustrator), Excel, Word, Facebook Ads and Page Manager, live DJ programs (Serato, rekordbox, vinyl), music production, commercial sewing/alterations